《女子监狱》
第二季第三集
好了  探访室在那边
All right, so you got your visiting room over here,
你爸妈来看你的时候就在那见面
which is where your mommy or daddy will come and visit you.
你得先把他们的名字列入探访名单
You gotta put their names on the list.
这边一块是禁区
This area, down here, out of bounds,
大家听好了  除非有安排...
okay, guys, until you get assigned down here...
他们关你肯定是为了你好
Ooh! They must've locked you up for your own good.
不用怕  姑娘
Hey, don't be afraid, little girl.
爹地可以保护你远离那些犯罪分子
Daddy can protect you from the criminal element.
好了大蹦  管好你的裤裆  好吗
All right, Boo, keep it in your pants, okay?
走吧  别理他们
Come on. Forget about them.
我的天
Oh, my God.
操  她又回来了
Oh, shit, she is risen!
妈的
Shit.
糟糕
我操
Oh, shit!
五  四  三  二  一  开始
Five, four, three, two, one, go!
这货谁啊  过
Man, I don't know who the fuck this is. Pass.
-不准过  -可我不知道啊
- Uh! No passing. - But I don't know...
大哥  别浪费时间
Man, time's running out!
就说  "跟什么音近"之类的
Say, like, "It sounds like," Or something.
好吧  韵脚跟布莱夫・布莱温一样
Uh, all right, rhymes with Bleve Blerwin.
靠  她作弊啊  不准说一样的韵脚
Man, she's cheating! You can't do no "Rhymes with"!
那我他妈还能咋样
What the fuck I was supposed to do?
谁知道这傻逼是谁啊
Stupid ass people ain't nobody ever heard of.
-时间到  -我知道了
- Time! - I know!
史蒂夫・厄尔温啊  主持《鳄鱼猎手》那个啊
Man, Steve Irwin. The Crocodile Hunter?
好走不送  傻逼没救
Rest in peace, B-T-dubs.
好了该我了  准备好了吗
All right, my turn! Ready, P?
我们赢定了
Whoo! We got this.
三  二  一  开始
And... three, two, one, go!
-相信外星人的傻哥们儿  -汤姆・克鲁斯
- Uh, crazy dude who believes in aliens? - Tom Cruise.
答对  好  好
Yes, ma'am. Okay, okay. Um...
-打篮球的  戴宅男眼镜  -勒布朗
- Basketball. Uh, nerd glasses. - LeBron.
-另一个  -韦德
- Other one. - D-Wade.
-没错  -搞毛啊
- Yes, ma'am. - Man, what the fuck?
一个女的  老公很年轻就死了
Yo, chick whose husband died real young.
-白人的米歇尔・威廉姆斯  -没错
- The white Michelle Williams! - Yes, yes.
时间到  你们没时间了
Time! You're outta time!
听着  只要你俩参加  我就不玩了
Uh-uh, now, see, as long as y'all two playing, I quit.
你不关注时事不能怪我们啊
Yo, yo, ain't our fault you ain't current on your US Weekly.
她们跟我们一样  麦肯锡
Stars, they're just like us, Mackenzie!
我能试试吗
Yo, you think I could try?
跟你说多少次了  得要你计时啊
Man, how many times I got to tell you we need you on clock duty?
当然  我喜欢计时
And I like clock duty.
盯着时间  感受时间
Yeah, watching the clock and smelling the clock.
可是呢  我在想
But, you know, I was thinking,
我这么有戏剧天分  我可以...
with my dramatic skills, I could play...
上次让你玩  你都差点疯了
Yo, son, you straight up lost your mind last time.
使劲打自己的头
All hitting yourself in the head and shit.
对啊  就因为你  我们都不能玩叠叠乐了
Yeah, we still can't play Jenga 'cause of you.
而且重点是  我们人数正好组两队
Yo, well, look, thing is, we already got a even number.
-好了  J  该你了  -去计时吧
- So, come on, J, you up. - Clock duty.
-来吧  J  -好吧
- All right, come on, J. - Okay.
五  四  三
And... five, four, three,
二  一
two, one.
发射喽
Blastoff!
我自己穿的  妈妈
I dressed myself, Mama!
她真美
She's so pretty.
是啊
Isn't she?
她就像你和爸爸
She looks like you and Daddy.
是妈妈和爸爸创造了她  宝贝
Mommy and Daddy made her, honey.
她是我们的奇迹
She's our miracle.
我能抱抱奇迹吗
Can I hold the miracle?
来  坐这儿
Here, sit back right here.
千万小心
Now, just be extra careful.
一定要拖住她的头
Make sure to support her head.
她叫什么
What's she called?
格蕾丝
Grace.
你好  格蕾丝
Hello, Grace.
我是你最好的朋友和姐姐  苏珊娜
I'm your best friend and your big sister, Suzanne.
我们是好朋友  就我俩
Just me and you. You and me. You and I.
好了亲爱的  可以了
Okay, honey, that's enough for now.
她今天累坏了  你可以晚点再抱她
She's had quite a journey today. You can hold her again later.
不行  她是我的  还给我
No! She's my baby! You give her back!
你说过她是我的
You told me she was mine!
她是我的  还给我  还给我
She's mine! Give her back! Give her back!
苏珊娜  别闹了  你是大孩子了
Suzanne, stop it, be a big girl.
做点什么
Do something.
-可我抱着孩子呢  -孩子给我
- But I have the baby! - Give her to me.
当姐姐感觉很兴奋吧
It's pretty exciting being a big sister, isn't it?
我弟弟刚出生的时候
You know, I couldn't wait
我简直迫不及待想见他
to meet my little brother when he was born.
可你知道吗  那孩子哭了整整一年
But you know what? That kid cried for a whole year.
我甚至问妈妈能不能把他塞回肚子里去
I even asked my mommy if she could put him back in her tummy.
要不要我帮你把头发弄一弄
Hey, would you like me to fix your hair up?
你穿的这么美  头发也得美美的才行啊
It seems you should have a fancy do to go with that fancy outfit.
我喜欢你的翅膀
Ooh! I love, love your wings.
谢谢  我最喜欢粉色了
Thank you, pink's my favorite color.
看得出来
Oh, I can see that.
真好看
Nice.
好了  查普曼
All right, there, Chapman.
看来今天是你的幸运日啊
Well, looks like it's your lucky day, hun.
来吧
Come on.
她们就像家人一样
It's like family.
我从没想过回到这里会这么高兴
Oh, I never thought I'd be so happy to be back here.
金发妞
Blondie!
我还以为你不会回来了呢
I thought they'd shipped you away for good.
我听说你给那女人好一顿揍啊
I heard you gave what's-her-boobs a pretty good beatdown.
都不知道你还有这本事
Didn't know you had it in you.
你把别人打了
You beat someone up?
没错  就是我
Yes, I did.
你叫什么来着  亲爱的
What's your name again, hun?
苏苏[一般]
Soso.
不  我是问你叫什么名字
No, no, no, I said what's your name?
这就是名字  布鲁克・苏苏
Yeah, that's my name. Brook Soso.
说来好笑  我爸妈想让我跟
Oh. Um, funny story, my parents
布鲁克・希尔兹同名  就是那个女演员
named me Brook after Brooke Shields, the actress.
但去掉了她名字里的"E"
Um, but except without the "E,"
因为他们觉得这样更像原创
'cause they thought it would be a bit more original.
可到了我十岁左右
But sometime around my 10th birthday,
他们又说取的是小溪的意思  原本就没有E
they started saying I was named after a brook instead.
就是说我话多
Um, like the babbling kind.
真有意思
That's funny.
又一次证明了  美貌与智慧不可兼得啊
Proving once again, you can either be pretty or smart.
没事  化疗让她脾气很差
Yeah, chemo makes her cranky.
不如你睡查普曼上铺吧  好吗
Why don't you take the bunk above Chapman, okay?
有东西给你  有牙刷
Oh, I got something for you. We got a toothbrush...
还有肥皂
and soap.
我通常不会这么通融的
I don't normally bend the rules like this,
不过你看起来也不是纯亚洲人
but you don't look full... Asia.
谢谢
Well, thank you.
真的  非常感谢
Seriously, for everything.
这跟我想象中的监狱太不一样了
This is not how I imagined prison to be at all.
她怎么了
What happened to her?
被烧伤了
Well, she got burned.
好了  我的车还有几分钟就要走了
Anyway, I got a van run in a couple of minutes.
罗莎  明天我送你去化疗时见
Rosa, I will see you tomorrow for your appointment.
对了  差点忘了
Oh! I almost forgot.
查普曼  牙刷刷和肥皂皂
Chapman, brushy brush and soapy soap.
我们都不知道你还会不会回来了
We didn't know if you were coming back.
是啊
Yeah.
我也是
Me, either.
还有剩吗
You have another one of those?
真不好意思  没了
Oh. I'm real sorry, hun, I don't.
你进来的时候那些黑姑娘没来看你么
One of the black girls didn't come round when you got in?
太遗憾了
That's a shame.
琳恩  我觉得自己像鸟一样自由
Leanne, I feel free as a bird.
不  也不是鸟  更像是蛇
No, like, not even a bird, like a snake! More like a snake.
像蟒蛇
Like an anaconda.
就好像  我要蜕掉那层旧皮
Like, I had to, like, shed that scaly skin
因为它不再适合我了  你明白吗
'cause it just didn't suit me anymore, you know?
你说话怎么像
Why are you talking like
手偶一样
one of those puppets with a hand up its butt?
我没有
I'm not.
我只是在微笑  看到没
I'm just smiling. See?
不管你怎么说
I don't care what you say,
他们在医院里肯定对你做了什么
they did something funny to you up in that hospital.
没错
Exactly!
你觉得我有什么不同了  我看起来怎么样
What do you think is different about me? How do I look?
不知道  感觉有点智障
I don't know, you're acting a little, like, retarded.
我才不智障  我换牙了
I'm not retarded, I got new teeth!
你嫉妒了
You're jealous.
才没有
No.
你是嫉妒我现在漂亮了  而你不漂亮吗
Are you jealous that I'm kind of pretty now and you're not?
我妈说漂亮是形容花朵和明星的
Mama says pretty's for flowers and movie stars,
因为二者都没什么脑子
'cause neither one's got a brain.
你什么意思  我没脑子吗
So, what are you saying? I'm not smart?
我是说...
Well, I'm saying...
我是说你表现得像你比我们优越似的
I'm saying you're acting like you're better than us,
我们不喜欢
and we don't like it.
好吧
Okay...
琳恩  也许你说的有点道理
You know what, Leanne, maybe you are onto something, all right?
也许我就是受够了待在这下面
Maybe I am tired of being down here,
折这些脏裤子
folding y'all's dirty panties, all right?
你他妈想听实话是吧
You wanna know the goddamn truth?
可能我就是想给自己
Maybe I wanna aim higher...
定个更高的目标
for myself.
好啊  塔琪
Yeah, you do that, Tucky.
你定得跟天花板一样高都没问题
You aim as high as the ceilings in here.
把天花板上人们弹上去的鼻涕
You might even be able to lick all the boogers
都给舔干净吧
people have flicked up there.
你还有其地方能待吗  随便哪儿
Do you have anywhere else to be? Anywhere?
没了  完全无处可去
Nope! Exactly nowhere to be.
那我只能另找个地儿了
Then I'll find somewhere else to be
你他妈太闹腾了
because you are annoying as shit.
我是被领养的  知道吗
I was adopted, you know.
恭喜你啊  我不是
Good for you. I wasn't.
你不是吗
Weren't you?
不是
No.
很遗憾听到你那么想
I'm sorry to hear you feel that way.
你根本不该来这儿
You're not even supposed to be in here.
我有我的办法
I got my ways.
我快脑充血了
There's so much blood rushin' to my head,
我都觉得像个虱子了
I'm starting to feel like a tick!
你知道的  它们会叮咬小鹿  就像...
You know how they bite a deer and then it's like...
别插话
Don't interrupt.
美味
Taystee...
那时候我必须躲起来
I had to go into hiding.
我出去的时候很需要你
I needed you when I was out...
可你到处都不见踪影
and you was nowhere to be found.
连个字条什么的都舍不得留
Couldn't even be bothered enough to leave a note or nothing.
宝贝  我也是出于无奈
Baby, that wasn't personal.
125大街开外的所有警察都在找我
I had every cop above 125th Street looking for me.
我不能告诉任何人我的行踪  太冒险了
I couldn't tell anybody where I was. It was too risky.
当然了
'Course not.
事情落到你身上时  你是一点险都不肯冒的
'Cause you ain't too good at risky when it comes to yourself.
在我老家  我们管这叫"胆小鬼"
Where I come from, we call that "Chicken shit."
我有我的理由
I had my reasons.
说实话  我觉得
You know, I'm feeling
我跟你浪费很多时间了
like I already gave you too much of my time.
我不需要你的解释  也不需要你
And I don't need your explaining, and I don't need you...
尤其是在这里
especially in here.
谢谢你让我说完
Thanks for being patient, letting me finish.
美味生你气了
Taystee mad at you?
是吗
Seems that way?
别太往心里去
Don't take it personal.
我就是这么做的
I try not to.
我知道你要说什么
Now, I know what you gonna say.
"可是苏珊娜  我心痛啊"
"But Suzanne, my heart hurts!"
我懂的  真的  十分了解
And I hear you, I do. A lot.
但你得低下头  给地板抛光
But you gotta put your head down, keep on buffing those floors.
顺时针转  然后逆时针转
Clockwise... and counter-clockwise.
有时候人们就是不想跟你玩
'Cause sometimes people just don't wanna play with you,
没关系
and that's okay.
你在维修队待过吗
You work on the maintenance crew?
待过  待过
I do. I do.
不过我的专长是抛光
My specialty is buffing, though.
很厉害
That's an impressive skill.
谢谢  谢谢你
Thank you, thank you.
对了  你是谁来着
by the way, who are you?
我叫维
I'm Vee.
很高兴见到你  苏珊娜
It's nice to meet you, Suzanne.
橙色服的那个
you in orange.
你过界了
You're out of bounds.
没穿上米色服前别让我在这儿看到你
Don't let me see you in here till you're wearing beige.
记住  只能吃一块蛋糕
Remember, only one piece of cake.
还有  苏珊娜
And, Suzanne,
别忘了戴你的夜用护牙板
don't forget to wear your night guard!
格蕾丝  姑娘们都在游戏室呢
Hi, Grace! The girls are in the game room.
她们正准备要看电影
They're just getting ready to watch a movie.
你们先上去参加派对吧
Why don't you girls go on down and join the party?
-好好玩  -妈妈再见
- Have a great time. - Bye. Mom!
希望你不介意
I hope you don't mind.
我们只是觉得让苏珊娜
We just feel it's important for Suzanne
跟格蕾丝一样进行社交活动很重要
to have the same social development as Grace.
我觉得苏珊娜在这儿不合适
I don't think it's appropriate for Suzanne to be here.
好吧  咱们有话直说  就因为她是黑人吗
Fine. Let's cut the bullshit, then, is this because she's black?
她都10岁了  这是6岁孩子的生日趴
She's 10 years old and it's a birthday party for 6-year-olds.
你知道这世上哪些孩子最煎熬吗  梅兰妮
You know which kids suffer in this world, Melanie?
就是那些被别人当做异类的孩子们
The ones who are told they're different.
那些不能跟同龄人一样
The ones who aren't given the opportunity to succeed
得到平等机会的孩子们
alongside every other kid their age.
我绝不会把自己的孩子定性为"异类"
And I'll be damned if I label my child "less than"
好让世界上的其他人用条条框框束缚她
so that the rest of the world can put her in a box
在她有机会成功之前就否定她
and dismiss her before she's had a chance to succeed in life.
我相信她今晚会玩得很开心的
I'm sure she'll have a great time tonight.
达娅
Daya.
待着别动  能听清我说话吗
No, just stay there. You... Can you hear me okay?
能听清
Yeah, I can hear you.
我没找到你  没想到你会来这儿
I couldn't find you. I didn't think you came here.
怎么  你觉得我不会看书
What, are you saying I don't read?
不  当然不是  我只是没想到...
What? No, of course not. I was just saying that I didn't...
这不像你会...
This isn't one of your typical...
抱歉  是荷尔蒙的原因
I'm sorry, it's the hormones.
我现在特别敏感
I'm real sensitive right now.
没关系
It's okay.
你还好吗
So, um, how's your day?
还行
Well, it's fine.
中午吃了点墨西哥菜  很棒
I had some special enchiladas for lunch. That was good.
你呢
How are you?
有点累
Uh, tired,
昨晚看比赛  很晚才睡
stayed up real late last night watching the game.
你在看什么书
What you reading there?
这有些孕期杂志之类的
They got pregnancy magazines and stuff in here.
这整篇文章都是写叶酸[维生素B]的
Look, this whole article is on folic acid.
听起来挺危险
That sounds dangerous.
不  其实对孩子很有好处
No, it's actually good for the baby and shit.
这里说如果服用这东西
It says we have better chances
有很大机会能避免孩子智障
of not having a retarded kid if I take it.
达娅  你不用担心这种事
Daya... Daya, you don't need to worry about stuff like that.
听着  我妈就没吃过维他命什么的
Look... my mom didn't take vitamins or whatever,
我敢说你妈妈也没吃过那些东西
and I think it's safe to say that yours didn't, either.
-这话什么意思  -没什么  我只是
- What's that supposed to mean? - Nothing. No, I just meant...
算了
Never mind.
-我希望比我妈妈更称职  -我明白
- I wanna be better than my mom. - I know...
我希望这个孩子能应有尽有
I want this baby to have everything.
我要告诉她们我怀孕了
I'm gonna tell them that I'm pregnant.
什么
What?
达娅  不能这么做
Daya, you can't do that.
要是孩子有事怎么办  约翰
What if there's something wrong with the baby, John?
达娅  我们谈过这事了
Daya, we have been over this.
反正半数的人都已经知道了  我不懂
Half of the girls know anyway. I don't get...
可是管理员不知道啊
But not the administration.
那又怎样  我不能
So what? I can't...
来自学啊  本尼特
Looking to educate yourself there, Bennett?
是啊  当然
Yeah. Yeah, totally.
Seventy-three hundred.
小心哦  没人喜欢博学的小白脸
Careful, no one likes a, uh, well-read beefcake.
我要看起来更猛点
I want to look fierce.
更风骚  还是更凶猛
Fierce? Fierce.
更凶猛
Second one.
不想再自怨自艾了  是吗
Tired of throwing them pity parties for yourself, huh?
我才不自怨自艾
I don't do pity.
亲爱的  你的发根可表达了相反的意思哦
Honey, those roots are saying otherwise.
德米特里这周末要来吗
Dmitri coming to visit this weekend?
不
No.
-里面有人了  -别傻了
- Somebody inside? - Don't be ridiculous.
如果不是为了性
If it ain't sex, what's got
你为啥舍得改变那灾难的发型了
you crawling out of that gutter of bad hair?
你有没有过看着镜子  想象别人是怎么看你的
Ever look at yourself and realize how other people must see you?
你了解了那种"姐以前是男人"的心情  是吧
You caught the whole used-to-be-a-man thing, right?
昨天  有个我很久之前认识的女人回来了
A woman I knew a long time ago came back in yesterday.
你想吸引她
So you wanna impress her?
应该说是想吓住她
More like intimidate her.
"别惹我"
"Don't fuck with me."
我正好有适合的颜色
I got just the color for that.
还有这些
And then these.
范妮  你信号不太好
I'm sorry, Franny, your reception's not so good.
我听成你说克里斯托弗要结婚了
It sounded like you said that Christopher's getting married.
他真要结婚了
He's gettin' married?
怎么会
Why would he?
他要搬到奥尔巴尼了
He's movin' to Albany?
我没  但是  天啊
I don't... But... Oh, my God.
是她
It's her.
他要搬去她那里
He's movin' into her house.
那里离这儿不到一小时路程
But that's less than an hour from here.
他这是故意要让我难受
He's tryin' to rub it in my face!
我他妈要勒死那个狗娘养的
I will fuckin' strangle that fuckin' cooze.
我知道  对不起  范妮  真的  对不起
I know, I know. I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Franny. No, no, I'm sorry.
我在努力了  真的
I'm tryin', I'm tryin'. I really am. Uh-huh.
亲爱的  我挂掉之前最后说一句
Now, honey, real quick, just before I go,
不如你告诉我是哪天吧
why don't you tell me when is it?
我他妈要是想知道  在报纸上也能找到
I can find a fuckin' newspaper if I want to.
赶紧告诉我
Just tell me when it is.
天啊  我是你姐妹
I'm your sister, for cryin' out loud.
可怜的宝贝  他好糊涂
My poor baby, he's so confused.
他还没意识到她是个婊子
He doesn't realize she's a whore.
既然有了蕾哈娜  就不该再勾搭杰茜卡・辛普森
You don't go Jessica Simpson when you got Rihanna.
是  我知道蕾哈娜是黑人  谢谢
Yes. Yes. Yes, I know that Rihanna is black, thank you.
可是...那我也知道
But... I know that, too.
好吧  好
Okay. All right.
我明白
Yes. Yes, I understand.
我会好好的  好
I'll be a good girl. Okay.
我也爱你  好  再见
I love you. I love you, too. Okay, bye.
天啊
God!
还好吗
Everything okay?
好得很
I'm great!
安德鲁吗  你好  我是莱瑞
Hey, Andrew? Hey, Larry.
谢谢你来见我
Of course. Thanks for meeting me.
我邮件里也说了  很喜欢你公共电台那篇文章
Uh, so, like I said in my email, loved your NPR piece.
谢谢
Oh, well, thanks.
我是《都市邮报》的忠实读者
Well, um, I read City Post religiously.
收到你的邮件我太兴奋了
I was really excited to get your email.
希望你能帮我联系帕波
I'm hoping you can put me in touch with Piper.
等等  为什么
Wait, what? Why?
我在写一个利奇菲尔德的报道  她能帮我
I'm doing a story on Litchfield. She's my way in.
你想挖什么
What's your angle?
诈骗  贪污
Fraud, embezzling.
他们申请了一个体育馆项目
They filed plans for a gym
两年前就该动工了
that supposedly broke ground two years ago.
有六千平方英尺  这可藏不住  对吧
We're talking 6,000 square feet. Hard to hide, right?
但你如果在谷歌地球上找  完全找不到影子
But when you look on Google Earth, no new structures.
-我操  -没错
- Holy shit. - Yeah, man.
我需要里面有个人  能帮我证实
I just need someone in there who can help corroborate
也许甚至能帮我打探点消息
and maybe, you know, sniff around for me.
我...
you know, I'm, uh...
我很热爱...
I'm pretty deep into, uh...
监狱题材的新闻
journalism with the prison story.
不只是帕波
Um, you know, and it's not just Piper.
她的律师和我也有定期联系
I mean, her counselor and I? We talk regularly,
所以  我会是个很有价值的人
so, yeah, I mean, I'd be a really great asset.
太好了
Great.
告诉丹妮丝
You tell Denise I don't
不管她妈从《今日秀》里听到了什么
care what her mother heard on The Today Show.
我这儿就只有面筋
I got nothing here gluten-free.
所以她要是死于面筋服用过量什么的
So if she dies from a gluten overdose or whatever,
我可阻挡不了她的命运
then who am I to stand in the way of fate?
进了监狱就得吃面筋
Prison is gluten.
不能吃面粉就他妈别犯罪啊  懂吗
Don't commit the crime if you can't fuckin' have flour, got it?
拿着  我自己去跟她说
Here, I'll tell her myself.
喂  还有绿色蔬菜吗
Hey, you gettin' any more greens up in here?
我想念以前的奶油玉米了
Yo, I miss that creamed corn, man.
就是
Word!
我还想给自己来点椰汁饮料  再点根烟呢
Yeah, well, I'd give my left tit for a pia colada and a smoke,
可菜单上也没有啊对吧
but you don't see that on the menu, right?
椰汁饮料听起来倒是不错
Pia colada do sound good, though.
好了
All right.
你跟我  咱俩现在就像快手姐妹一样  对吧
So you and me, we're, like, snatch sisters now, right?
能不聊我前女友的阴道吗
Can we not talk about my ex-girlfriend's vagina?
我不想这么较真
I hate to be a stickler here,
不过应该说是前女友/情妇/毁掉你生活的人吧
but isn't it more like ex-girlfriend-mistress-life-ruiner?
大伙儿
Is everybody...
大伙儿现在是不是都盯着我呢
Is everybody staring at me right now?
我真心有种众目睽睽的感觉
Because I really feel like everyone's staring at me.
真高兴看到你进步了  查普曼
It's great to see you evolving, Chapman.
你已经克服了
And getting past the whole
"我是所有人生命的主角"的自恋情结
"I'm the star of my own movie and everyone else's, too" Complex.
我真会那样吗
Do I do that?
知道吗  你真的伤了她
You know, you really hurt her.
我不想聊这个
I don't wanna talk about that.
她像只受伤的小羊一样跑来找我
She came running to me like an injured lamb.
没错  小羊  戴着性感眼镜
Yes, a lamb with great, sexy glasses
奶子丰满柔软塞了我一嘴
and giant pillowy tits inside of my mouth.
艾丽克斯・沃斯可不是小羊
Alex Vause was never a lamb.
她是吃羊的母狼
She is the wolf that eats the lamb.
那也不能怪狼  谁让羊这么美味呢
You can't blame the wolf. Lamb's delicious, that's smart eating.
老实点  查普曼
Watch yourself, Chapman.
真不敢相信她出去了
Oh, I can't believe she got out.
体制就这么操蛋
System's fucked.
她们现在有你的号码了  亲爱的
They got your number now, honey.
你看什么
What are you looking at?
我就知道那些贱人在说谎
I knew them bitches was lying
她们说你离开的时候就像《火线》里的奥马尔
when they said you left here looking like Omar from The Wire.
你看  我就说大家都在讨论我吧
See, I told you everybody's talking about me.
别激动  奥马尔
Relax, Omar.
怎么  连我也想揍了吗
What, you gonna beat the shit out of me now, too?
告诉我安全词就让你上
Just tell me the safe word.
我想你了
I missed you.
我也想你
Yeah, I missed you, too.
你还好吗
You okay?
还行
Fine, fine.
就是最近有点焦虑
Just a little antsy lately.
我不会  这地方跟我前几周待的地方相比
Oh, not me. This place is a spa compared to where I've been
简直就是温泉度假村
for the past few weeks.
我就说那水有股黄瓜味嘛
I thought the water tasted like cucumbers.
听起来就像个噩梦
Man, it sounds like it was a fucking nightmare.
我花了很长时间想  我死了会有影响吗
I spent a lot of time wondering if it would matter if I died.
宏观上说  没有
In the macro sense, no.
你就是生活宝箱里的一个玩具
You're one Cheerio in the bulk box of life,
但是  你能让我高兴  所以我在意
but... you fuckin' tickle me, so I think it would matter.
辛迪是吧
Cindy, right?
看情况
Depends.
听说你在仓库工作
I'm told you work in the warehouse.
不  现在有份好差事  做大腿舞女
Nah, got a real sweet gig as a Rockette right now.
能帮我办点事吗
Would you be willing to do an errand for me?
你还真有礼貌啊
Well, ain't you real polite,
居然想说漂亮话找免费工作
using your white folks' words to get free work.
我在一个电源插座里藏了点东西
I have something hidden in one of the electrical sockets
就在他们堆坏箱子那边的墙脚
behind where they stack the broken down boxes.
如果你能帮我取来  我会非常感谢的
I'd be very grateful if you could retrieve it for me.
贱人
Bitch...
感谢值钱的话  我们早成比尔・盖茨了
if grateful paid the bills, we'd all be Bill Gates.
懂我意思吗
Know what I'm sayin'?
漏了一块  那儿
Missed a spot, right there.
给
Here.
苏茜  今天你想睡金花鼠的
Suzie, you want the Chipmunks
还是布偶娃娃的睡袋呢
or the Muppet Babies sleeping bag this time?
-出去  我换衣服呢  -那又怎样
- Get out of here, I'm changing. - So?
我已经快成为一个女人了
I'm starting to become a woman,
妈妈说不能让人看到我穿泳衣的部分
and Mom says I shouldn't let people see my bathing suit parts.
今晚我睡布偶娃娃的
I'll take the Muppets tonight.
求你别装怪
Please don't be weird.
我没装怪
I'm not weird.
我跟大家一样
I'm just like everyone else.
"从前  有个非常非常美丽的女孩..."
"Once upon a time, there was an extra pretty girl... "
然后  格蕾丝  你来编下一段
And then, Grace, you go, make up the next part,
-然后我们轮流来  -好
- and then we'll go around the circle. - Okay.
从前  有个非常非常美丽的女孩
Once upon a time... there was an extra pretty girl
她和家人住在山顶的一栋大房子里
who lived in a huge house on top of a hill with her family.
但是  恶龙闯来了
But then a dragon came swooping in,
从鼻孔里
breathing fire out of its
喷出火焰  点燃了房子
dragon nostrils and lights the house on fire.
她的家人有的跑了出去
Some of her family runs outside,
但小女孩却自己困在了里面
but the little girl gets trapped inside by herself.
她哭喊着求救
She screams for help,
但没人想回去救她
but no one wants to come back and save her,
她独自坐在那里哭泣着
so she sits and she cries by herself...
最后孤独地被火活活烧死了
and gets burned up by the fire and dies alone.
不是这样的
That's not how it goes.
可这样才有意思啊
But now it's more interesting.
不  这太蠢了
No! That's stupid.
你真蠢
You're stupid.
但龙很酷啊
But dragons are cool.
布鲁克  布鲁克  布鲁克
Hey, hey, hey, Brook. Brook? Brook?
我还以为大家都喊姓呢
I thought everyone goes by their last names.
是的
They do,
但我现在没法一本正经地喊你的姓
but I can't say yours with a straight face right now, so...
试着深呼吸
Try to take some deep breaths.
深呼吸  深呼吸  好的
Deep breaths. Deep breaths, okay.
你要跟我一起呼吸一下吗  查普曼
Do you wanna take some breaths with me, Chapman?
不用了
No.
以前我在齐尼亚的一个胡桃木农场WWOOF时
You know, when I was WWOOFing on a walnut farm in Xenia...
你干嘛来着
While you were what-ing?
WWOOF  就是在有机农场当志愿工人
WWOOFing. Willing Workers On Organic Farms.
齐尼亚在哪
Where is Xenia?
俄亥俄州
It's in Ohio.
你以后最好说"在俄亥俄州当志愿者"
You should probably just say "Volunteering in Ohio" From now on.
不然的话太让人困惑了
It's pretty misleading otherwise.
好的
Okay, well...
梅朵[牧场]说了件特别有意思的事
Meadow said this really amazing thing...
牧场
Meadow?
还是个人名
Is that a person?
人名  她是我最好的朋友
Yeah, she's my best friend.
曾经是我最好的朋友
Was my best friend.
总之  她说
Anyway, she said...
"布鲁克  当个小蝗虫"
"Brook, be a grasshopper."
简直说得太对了  你懂吗
And it just made so much sense, you know?
不懂
No, I don't.
那是生活的同步性  查普曼
It's about the synchronicity of life, Chapman.
我好想她
I miss her so much.
-梅朵  -没事的  会好的
- Meadow. - It's fine. It's gonna be fine.
你看起来真冷静
You seem so calm.
你是杀人犯吗
Are you a murderer?
不  我不是杀人犯
No, I'm not a murderer!
别跟我吼  我现在特别害怕
Don't yell at me! I'm really scared right now!
-小点声  -好  我知道  我知道
- Shut up! - Hey, hey, hey. Okay, I know, I know.
知道吗  我第一天来这也哭了一晚
You know, I cried my whole first night, too.
会好的  你会习惯的
It gets easier. You'll adjust.
你会交到新朋友
You'll find friends, and pretty
而且很快  这些食物也不会那么难以下咽了
soon the food is not gonna make you dry-heave
而且你还会掌握边跟人互瞪
and, you know, you'll even get the hang of pooping
边拉屎的窍门
while making eye contact with somebody.
凡事都会结束  布鲁克
Everything ends, Brook.
刑期也有尽头
Even prison.
试着多想想这点
Try to focus on that.
这儿有纸巾
Here are some tissues.
我想我已经找到朋友了
I think I'm finding friends already.
好  好了
Okay, all right.
要我去看看吗  已经45分钟了
Should I go check on the table? It's been 45 minutes.
我相信女主人能做好她的事
I'm sure the hostess is good at her job.
也对
Right.
-要再来一杯吗  -不用
- Do you want another drink? - I'm good.
帕波怎么样了
So how's Piper doing?
-什么  -帕波  你牢里那位前未婚妻
- Pardon? - Piper? Your ex-fiance who's in prison?
这...
It's...
你向我打听她  感觉有点怪
It feels... weird that you're asking me about her.
我要是装作对你一无所知不是更奇怪吗
Well, would it be weirder if I pretended not to know about you?
即使你爸没跟我说过
Because, you know, even if your dad hadn't told me,
现在都21世纪了
it is the 21st century
谷歌上轻轻一点
and a quick click on Google
就能找到任何想要的信息
can give me any information that I need, so...
我喜欢有点效率  咱就别寒暄了吧
I like efficiency. Let's just skip the small talk.
我...我不知道帕波怎么样了
I don't... I don't know how Piper is.
-我们现在没联系了  -够聪明
- We're not speaking at the moment. - Smart.
抱歉  我爸说你是儿科医师之类的
Uh, I'm sorry, my dad said you were a pediatrician of some sort?
小儿神经专家
Pediatric neurologist.
这就是我
Here I am,
29岁  是家长们特别喜欢的类型
29 years old and really impressive to parents.
-你跟他们一起住吗  -跟谁
- Do you live with them? - Who?
你的父母
Your parents.
什么  不
What? No.
没说  他这么说吗
No, did he say that?
只是觉得他们好像跟你互动挺多的
What, no, it's just, they seem pretty involved in your life.
对  这倒是
Yeah. Yeah, they are.
你现在有什么工作项目吗
So you working on anything right now?
当然  我...
Yeah, you know, I mean...
我在做一些抉择
I'm considering some options.
我在试着弄清下一步要做什么
I'm trying to figure out what's next.
太好了
Oh, no, that's great.
我实在厌倦了每次相亲
I... You know, I am just so tired of going on dates
就听那些男的不停地说啊说啊
where I have to listen to guys go on and on
说他们怎么把推特的内容写成博客
about how they're turning their Twitter feeds into blogs,
把博客出版成书
their blogs into books,
然后又把书的内容更新到推特
and their books into Twitter feeds.
听这些废话太累人了
It's exhausting.
就别假装播客还算工作了  对吧
Stop pretending that your podcast is work, right?
对
Right.
不  只是
No, it's just...
你什么都没做真是让人眼前一亮
it's really refreshing that you're not doing anything.
是吗
Yeah?
真的  挺好的
No, it's great.
没有野心的男人是我的首选
A guy without ambition is at the top of my list.
我就想找个心甘情愿在家带三个小孩的
Someone who's happy to stay at home with our three kids
而我则负责应酬其他人
while I take care of other people's.
你想要孩子吗  你的脸书主页没写
Did you want kids, because your Facebook profile didn't say?
小点声
Shut up.
有人吗
Hello?
迪亚茨  你床铺这边太脏了
Diaz, your side of the bunk is looking dirty.
我建议你赶快用卫生棉擦擦地板
I suggest you take a maxi pad to that floor, stat,
如果你想通过检查的话
if you wanna pass inspection.
收到我的礼物了吗
Did you get my gift?
嗯
Yeah.
怎么了  我还以为你会很激动呢
What's wrong? I... I thought you'd be excited.
是啊  能认识一个在我枕头下放生菠菜
Yeah, I've been dreaming about meeting a man
还写着"给我的宝贝"的男人
who will leave a bag of raw spinach underneath my pillow
简直是我梦寐以求的
with a note that says, "For my baby."
你还真是个白马王子啊
You're a real Prince Charming.
去他妈的钻石  我就爱菠菜
Fuck diamonds, I got spinach!
菠菜含有维生素B  是富含
Spinach has folic acid in it. A lot.
而且  我选的还是有机品种
And... I even got the organic kind.
同事现在都叫我大力水手了
The guys up front are calling me Popeye now.
他们还以为是我的午餐呢
They think it's my lunch!
约翰  我不需要每天一袋菠菜
John, I ain't gonna eat a whole bag of spinach every day.
我他妈不是兔子
I'm not a fucking rabbit.
反正分娩前的维他命
The pre-natal vitamins
已经有所需的一切营养了
have all kinds of other stuff in them, anyway.
我...
Look, I...
我不能弄药进来  达娅  对不起
I can't get the pills in, Daya, I'm sorry.
我们兜里都不能揣维他命
Look, we're not even allowed to have vitamins in our bags now.
明早七点开始检查  迪亚茨
I'll reinspect tomorrow at 7:00 a.M., Diaz.
如果你不想关心我们宝宝的健康
If you're not gonna be concerned about the health of our child,
如果你不愿意想办法
and you don't wanna figure this out,
-知道吗  -天啊
- then you know what? - Oh, my God...
-我受够了  -别学你妈妈的语气
- I'm done. - ... please do not talk like your mother.
这
It's...
这挺吓人的
it scares me.
我们能不能
Hey, can we, uh...
能不能一会在老地方见
Can we meet at our spot later?
我想摸摸你
I miss touching you.
去吧
Go.
你干什么呢
What are you doing?
我看到蒲公英了
I saw Dandelion.
重来  你想说什么
Try again. What... what are you trying to say?
帕波
Piper.
她讨厌我
She hates me.
她很危险
She's dangerous,
不过我也很危险
but so am I.
谁  那个白人女孩吗
Who? That white girl?
天啊  苏珊娜
Oh, man, Suzanne.
听我说  好吗
Listen to me, okay?
我那个年代  这地方可是黑人女人说了算
In my day, the black women ran this place.
我说是"女人"  因为那才是我们的本质
And I say women, because that's what we were.
女人
Women.
不是一群带着坏脾气到处撒野的小女孩
Not a bunch of little girls running around here with bad attitudes.
我看到你了  明白吗  我看清你了
Now, I see you, you understand? I see you.
你是个聪明  强壮的黑人女人
You're a smart, strong, black woman.
这里的人都小看你  但我不会
Everybody else around here underestimates you, but not me.
下次见到蒲公英还是谁的
You remember that the next time you run into Dandelion,
记住我的话
or whatever the hell you wanna call her.
把头抬高了  听到了吗
You hold your head up high, you hear me?
说到底  你才是花园中盛放的玫瑰
Because at the end of the day, you are a garden rose,
而那贱人只是棵杂草
and that bitch is a weed.
谢谢你给我这个
Thank you for these.
很高兴
It's...
很高兴能在这里交到个朋友
it's good to know I have a friend in here.
操他妈  尼古拉斯  你得提高点技术了
Jesus fucking Christ, Nichols, you gotta work on your technique.
我上她们的时候没人能撑这么久还不高潮的
No babe ever takes this long when I'm doing her.
知道吗  有的坚果就是比其他的硬
You know, some nuts are tougher to crack than others.
得了吧  两指进去
Oh, please, two in the pink,
一指搓点  又不是什么高科技的活
one in the stink. It ain't rocket science.
我马上就出来了
Hey, I'll be out in a second!
爽  天啊  爽
Yes! Oh, my God! Yeah!
触底得分
We have a touchdown.
我们不处理什么过敏请求了
We're no longer accommodating any bullshit allergy requests.
听着  我只是来告诉你
Listen, I'm just here to tell you that...
昨晚的哈瓦那酱汁简直跟拉利卡餐馆有一拼
the habanero sauce last night at dinner was almost as good as La Rica's.
你怎么知道拉利卡
How you know La Rica?
纽约最棒的辣酱
Spiciest salsa in New York.
你学得很像啊
Oh, yeah, you're a good imitator.
我就当你这是好话了
I'll take that as a compliment.
本来就是好话
It was meant as such.
我是维
I'm Vee.
欢迎来到监狱
Welcome to prison.
应该是欢迎又来了
Welcome back, actually.
我在想  我们能不能
I was just wondering, if we could...
做个交易
make a trade.
盖子打开
Flip the top.
都到齐了  是吧  查普曼  欢迎回来
Well, the gang's all here, huh? Chapman, welcome back.
德盖特小姐  你看起来...精神很好
Miss Doggett, you're looking... rested.
没看出来  真的吗
Uh? No? Really?
没发现我的新牙吗
You didn't notice my teeth?
靠
Dang it.
我换了新牙  因为她把我的旧牙打掉了
Well, I got new teeth, 'cause she knocked my old ones out.
我想我们都不能否认
I think we can all agree there were some...
你在打架前就有牙齿问题了  德盖特小姐
dental issues before the fight, Miss Doggett.
卡普托先生  我只想说
Mr. Caputo, I would just like to say
我已经准备好当一个模范狱友了
that I am prepared to behave like a model inmate
我觉得我已经构不成威胁了
and I feel I no longer pose a threat.
省省吧  查普曼  这不是选美比赛
Spare us, Chapman, this isn't a beauty pageant.
我想见你们两个  好一起来把这事解决好
I wanted to see you both so we can put this all behind us.
既往不咎
Bury the hatchet...
或者其他出处
or something with a little less violent history
不那么暴力的成语
than that particular idiom.
从管理部门的角度来看  你们都有错
From an administration perspective, you're both found at fault.
解决了
Case closed.
可她并没打我
But she didn't hit me.
我钦佩你的特立独行  查普曼
While I admire your incessant need to be special, Chapman...
她的确动手了
she did.
不不不  我不是那个意思
No, no, no, no, no, that's not what I meant.
除非你想解释一下  你怎么会躺在雪里
Unless you'd like to explain how else you wound up in the snow
脸被打伤了
with your face bashed in...
我猜也是
Ah, I didn't think so.
我想  你挨了德盖特小姐几拳
I presume your ego will be all right
自尊心不会太受不了吧
with Miss Doggett getting a few punches in,
毕竟你俩
seeing as how you're both
都去了低安全级别设施享受了一阵
enjoying the cozy comforts of minimum security
而不是在禁闭室里关到烂
instead of rotting away in the SHU.
我想  我们都两清了吧  女士们
I'd like to assume we're all squared away here, ladies.
我可以
Well? Can I?
这么想吗
Assume that, huh?
很好
Good.
也许你们能...
Perhaps you'd like to, uh...
拥抱一下
hug?
帮我确认你们已经言归于好了
To help assure me of your new friendship?
你说真的吗
Are you serious?
很好  你们可以走了
Good, okay, you may go.
平安与你们同在
Peace be with you.
出去关上门
Close the door behind you.
不
No.
你一点都没变
Well, you haven't changed a bit.
我相信还是有一点变化的
Oh! I'm sure there are a few differences.
你还好吗
You've been well?
本来再好不过了  可惜又回到了这里
Never better, till I landed back in here.
都怪那些新法律  不好混啊
All the new drug laws these days. Nasty business.
昨天在厕所你没跟我打招呼
You didn't say hello to me in the bathroom yesterday.
我没看到你在厕所  你看错了
I didn't see you in the bathroom. You're mistaken.
当然
I must be.
很遗憾你不在厨房工作了
I'm sorry to see that you're not in the kitchen.
现在的食物真是  不咋地
The food now is... no bueno.
也许有助于你减肥
Perhaps that will help with your weight.
是吗  起码黑人不长皱纹
Yeah, well, at least black don't crack.
你说得对  一切都没变
You're right, nothing has changed.
红妈啊  我老了  混不开了
Oh, Red, I'm getting too old for this shit.
我才回来两天
I've been back here two days
就发现规矩全变了
and already I can see the game has changed.
是啊
It has.
我想这次我就老老实实的吧
I think this time I'm just gonna keep my head down,
看点书  顺上帝的旨意  好好服刑
read my books, do my time like the good Lord intended.
这把老骨头需要平静平静了
These old bones just need a little bit of peace and quiet.
听起来不错
That sounds nice.
有野心  而且是胡扯  但挺好
Ambitious, and bullshit, but nice.
你可以的  宝贝  你做好热身准备了吗
You're gonna be great, honey. You did your scale warm-ups?
现在有请  苏珊娜・沃伦
And now I'd like to introduce Suzanne Warren,
她将带来一支特别的毕业之歌
who will be singing a special graduation song.
去吧亲爱的  这是你的机会
Come on, sweetie, this is your chance.
让他们看看你有多棒
Go show them how great you are.
不  我不行
No, I can't!
我做不到  妈妈  我不行
I can't do it, Mom! No! Mom, I can't do it!
我不行  不行
I can't! I can't! I can't!
我不行
I can't!
感谢主
Praise the Lord
我看见了光
I saw the light
我是如此快乐  痛苦都不见
Now I'm so happy, no sorrow in sight
感谢主  我看见了光
Praise the Lord, I saw the light
我觉得整个人都重生了
Ooh, I felt alive with the spirit!
就像穿着熊衣服的耶稣宝宝
Like baby Jesus in the bear suit!
我能感觉到他的存在
I felt his presence.
你感觉到他的存在
You felt his presence...
还是你觉得尿从两腿间流下来了
or did you feel pee running down your leg?
如果还要哑巴来救你  那就真是糟透了
Yo, you know shit is bad when the mute has to save you.
哑巴
The mute.
再来一次  怎么弄的  这样吗
Go ahead, how's it go? How does it go? Like this?
我做对了吗
Am I doing it right?
不  妈妈
No, Mommy!
我不想的
I don't want to!
你老是逼我做这些事
You're always pushing me to do these things!
逼我
Pushing me!
够了  妈妈
No more, Mommy!
够了
No more.
能跟你聊聊吗
Can I talk to you?
我很抱歉  请别生我的气
I'm real sorry for what I did. Please don't be mad at me.
不不  苏珊娜
No, no, Suzanne...
苏珊娜  你救了我
Suzanne, you saved me.
不  我打了你
No, I hit you.
打在脸上
In your face.
是  但是...
Yes, I... But you...
你让那看起来像一场斗殴
You made it look like it was a fair fight.
就是因为你  我才能回来
You are the whole reason I am back here.
我真的很感激你
I am so grateful to you.
今晚想一起看电影吗
Do you wanna go see the movie tonight together?
不行  蒲公英
No, I don't think so, Dandelion.
我是花园中的玫瑰
I'm a garden rose.
无聊
怎么了  孩子
What's going on, kid?
你又梦到鼻音先生了吗
Did you have another dream about Mr. Snuffles?
那个婊子偷了我的日子
That whore is stealing my date!
什么  你要出去了吗
What? Are you getting out?
不  我的婚礼日子
No, no, my wedding date!
克里斯托弗要在我的婚礼日子结婚
Christopher's getting married on my date.
可是新娘不是我
Just like we were supposed to.
这...真遗憾
Hey, it's... I'm sorry.
我知道他就是想伤害我
Oh, I know he's doing it just to hurt me.
有哪个女人不想自己选结婚的日子啊
What kind of a woman doesn't wanna pick her own date?
对婚礼的复杂程序不感兴趣
Someone who doesn't get excited by the wedding industrial complex
也不喜欢社会非要拿女人当小孩哄的人
and society's bullshit need to infantilize grown women.
而且她还那么胖
And she's fat!
是啊  真是个荡妇
Yeah, that's a slut.
来
Come here.
去他妈的克里斯托弗
Fuck Christopher.
他肯定是给男人口交的
I bet he sucks dicks.
你干嘛呢
What are you doing?
我很好  查普曼
I'm really good, Chapman.
不  我是问你在干嘛
No, I said "What" Are you doing.
在为我这一整天定目标
Just setting my intention for the day.
回你自己床上定去
Well, set your intention on your own bed.
你太像梅朵了  简直要了我的命
You are so much like Meadow, it kills me.
知道吗  传统来说女人比男人更能接受公有
You know, traditionally, women are much more communal than men.
所以大部分女性不那么暴力
That's why most women are less violent.
我在一本写巴布亚新几内亚的母权制的书里看的
I read that in a book about matriarchy in Papua New Guinea.
总之  我觉得如果你能更乐意分享一些
Anyway, I think that if you shared a bit more easily,
也许你就不会揍那个女孩了  知道吗
maybe you wouldn't have beat that girl up, you know?
不  苏苏
No, Soso,
我不知道
I don't know.
谁他妈也听不懂你在说什么
No one has a fucking clue what you are talking about, ever,
而且我也不需要你的建议
and I definitely do not need your advice.
从不
Ever.
我们不是朋友  我不是你的新保护毯
We are not friends, I am not your new safety blanket,
我也绝对不会成为你的新梅朵
and I am definitely not going to be your new Meadow.
我是头独狼  布鲁克
I am a lone wolf, Brook.
凶恶的独狼
And a vicious one.
别逼我用獠牙撕开你的喉咙
Don't make me rip your throat out with my teeth.
-维兹  -李尔・韦恩
- Weezy. - Lil Wayne!
你不能那样说他们的名字
Nah! You can't be all sayin' their names like that!
-时间到  -我什么也没说
- Time! - Yo, I ain't say shit.
那是他的昵称
That's his nickname.
就跟这样提示乔治・杰弗逊是一样的
And it could've just as easy been a George Jefferson reference.
那贱人怎么回事
Yo, what's the deal with that bitch, anyway?
反正我不喜欢
I don't like her.
找我帮忙来着  好像她是这里老大似的
Asking favors already, like she own the damn place.
有几个女孩说  她以前还真是
She used to. That's what some of the girls were saying.
我才不管过去  我活在当下
I don't care 'bout no "Used to." I live in the present.
合十礼什么的
Namaste and shit.
那是维
That's Vee.
等等  传说中的那个维
Hold up, like... like "Vee," Vee?
对
Yep.
你怎么不早说
Why you ain't say nothing?
维是他妈哪根葱
Uh, who the fuck is Vee?
T的老妈
Basically, like T's mom.
谢谢
Gracias.
苏珊娜  过来吃点蛋糕
Suzanne! Come get you some cake.
为啥她有蛋糕吃
Why she get some cake?
为啥我们没有  她以为她是谁啊
Why can't we get no cake? Who she think she is?
你好啊  美味
Hey, Taystee Girl.
以示友好
Peace offering.
巧克力糖霜加彩糖
Funfetti with chocolate icing.
你怎么...你到底...
How did you... like, what did you...
我找人帮了点忙
I get by with a little help.
苏珊娜帮了大忙
Suzanne here played a big part.
原谅我吧
Forgive me.
我保证再也不会让你失望了
I promise I will never let you down again.
那些年我不一直陪着你吗
Wasn't I there for you all those years?
我不是一直在照顾你吗
Didn't I take care of you?
让我在这里也做同样的事吧
Let me do the same here.
不如
Why don't you, uh...
邀请你的朋友过来吧
invite your friends to join us?
这蛋糕浪费了太可惜了
Be a shame to waste all this cake.
这位是维  这是...
This is Vee. Vee, this is...
我都知道
Yeah, yeah, I know.
珍娜  辛迪
Janae, Cindy,
珀比
Poussey.
姑娘们
Ladies...
饿了吗
are you hungry?
话说  你们刚才玩的是什么游戏
So, what was that game y'all were just playing?
人数是奇数就玩不了  不好意思
Don't work with an uneven number. No offense.
我数着有六个人啊
Well, I count six of us.
得有人计时
Someone needs to keep time.
大家可以轮流计时嘛
Well, everybody can take turns keeping time.
要不
You think, maybe,
咱门可以混合组队  对吧
we should mix up them teams, right? Don't you think?
当然可以
I don't see why not.
知道吗  我对你有种感觉
You know, I had a feeling about you.
我就知道我们合得来
Knew we would get along.
你满嘴屁话  眼睛都是屎黄的
Man, you so full of shit, your eyes brown.
我来帮你  宝贝
Here, let me help you with that, baby.
我觉得是时候给你换个新造型了  苏茜
You know, I think it's time we found you a new look, Suzie.
可我一直都是这个发型
Oh, but this is how I've always done it.
也许是时候把它们释放出来了
Maybe it's time to just, you know, air it out a little bit.
这烟简直是垃圾  哪来的啊  过期了吧
These are stale as fuck! Where'd you get these, 1983?
妈逼的
Motherfucker.